"Doing Whatever You Want with the Magic Hand"
Awesome, it's the comic I've always wanted!
Looks pretty interesting
Gian, no!
I bought this comic with my own money!
What's yours is Gian's!
And what's mine is mine!
How can you do that?
Poor Nobita
He's practically the most pitiful boy in the world!
And that's what happened
Is there any way to help this poor boy?
That's so ridiculous
Besides, it's not even snowing right now!
It's just to express how I felt back then
Getting my comic stolen really did happen!
Then I'll just help you get your comic back
"Magic Hand"
Remember, you can't use this gadget to do bad things!
Yeah, yeah, I know
I'm off!
Is this really going to be okay?
Let's see, where is Gian?
Such an interesting comic is totally wasted on Nobita
All right
Grabbed the wrong one
Where is it?
Darn that Gian!
Take this!
Who's there?
It really felt like someone was twisting my ear just now
Whatever, then
Who is that?!
What's going on?!
Total success!
Seems like you went a bit too far
Doraemon
Take the comic home for me
I'm going to have some fun with these gloves before heading back
That's way too much!
You always do this, Nobita!
Whenever you get carried away...
You always end up doing bad things!
Don't be mad, don't be mad
*Tickle*...
Don't try to distract me! Give them back right now!
Give them back right now! Ow...
Give them back right now!
I really, really don't like your tone
So I'm not giving them back to you
Wait up!
If you dare, just try coming over!
That's so mean!
This looks so realistic
Nobody would ever believe it's fake
Let's go test it on Nobita right away
Let's have you try it out first!
Th-This...
It's a real snake!
Help me, Mom!
That's what you get for doing that to me!
Found you! Give the Magic Hand back!
What? Right when it's getting fun!
Darn it!
Where would you like to go, passenger?
I didn't want a ride!
Hang on tight!
That takes care of that
Oh right, it'd be nice to go show Shizuka
I'm so sorry!
Nobita!
Oh, again?
I'll never forgive you!
Do you want to help me carry this?
- Yes
- Really?
- Kids these days are so kindhearted
- It's nothing, really
My, that really deserves praise
You've gone too far!
It's a bit too early to use it now
What is Shizuka doing?
I get it!
She really wants to try her mom's makeup
In that case, let me help her out!
Why?
This is harder than I thought!
No matter what, I have to make Shizuka pretty!
Sorry!
Shizuka really looks better without makeup after all
She's cute enough just the way she normally is
Really?
Your son's blind date didn't go well yesterday?
Yeah
But these things come down to fate in the end
I'm sure your son will find a great match
Why is this happening?
Ma'am, what are you doing?
It's my body!
I'm so tired!
I'm sorry, my body's moving on its own!
This is getting way out of hand!
Now I have no choice but to use that method
Pulling such an outrageous prank...
It has to be you, Nobita!
That's right, exactly!
How horrible!
It wasn't me!
I'll definitely catch you red-handed!
The Magic Hand is used from far away
so no one can catch me
Ouch!
How could this be?
(Magic Butt)
This is the Magic Butt
As long as you hit this
you can punish them no matter where they are
This is punishment for your pranks!
Nobita!
"Snake-Headed Monster"
I'm home!
You're back?
What's wrong? You can't even stand properly?
Massage my legs for me
What's the matter with you?
Why should I massage your legs?
Because I was made to stand all day at school
so my legs are exhausted now
If that's the case, you should be more careful
and not get punished by the teacher
That's impossible
I'm fully confident
that I'll still forget my homework in the future
and fall asleep during class, too
Why be so confident about something so shameful?
So give me a gadget that won't make me tired when standing for punishment
You're hopeless...
"Snake-Headed Monster"
What's this box with a snake head?
Li... Listen to me
This is an extremely terrifying gadget
So you must use it very carefully, okay?
The beam of light emitted from its eyes
can completely harden a creature's muscles
turning them just like stone
I don't want such a scary gadget!
It's fine, if you use it carefully
it's actually a very handy gadget
Really?
Now, aim it at your legs
and slowly open the lid
I... I can't move them!
My legs have turned to stone!
See, isn't that perfect?
With stone legs, you won't get tired no matter how long you stand
Hey, you're right
In that case, even standing for days would be fine
All you have to do is pull its snake-like hair
and it'll turn back to normal
Great, then I'll take it to school tomorrow
Is getting punished really something to look forward to?
Nobita, go stand in the hallway!
Yes, sir
This is so easy
It feels just like sitting on a rock
There are plenty of other uses too
Like turning everyone I hate into stone
Though doing that isn't very nice, is it?
Why not harden my fists
and go teach Gian a lesson?
He'll definitely be seeing stars!
That would feel so satisfying
Just thinking about it makes me happy
Nobita
Uh... Sir?
Do you think being punished to stand is fun?
No, of course not
Stay standing here until school ends!
Just keep standing then!
I got chewed out by the teacher, too
-Nobita
-Yes, sir
Let me remind you again
Make sure you finish your sketch homework
Right... okay
Goodbye
So frustrating!
What is this?
I'm back
I'm exhausted
Massage my legs
Huh?
Didn't you use the Snake-Headed Monster today?
I forgot to bring it back!
I accidentally left it at school
Oh no, this is bad!
Anyone who gets close turns into stone!
What are we going to do?
Honestly, so annoying!
Who left this kind of junk in the hallway?
What on earth is this?
Looks like there's something inside
That sound just now...
It's the Snake-Headed Monster!
It came from behind the school
Whoa, could it be...
Let's go check
Teacher!
Teacher has turned into stone!
The Snake-Headed Monster did this
In that case, where's the Snake-Headed Monster?
It...
got out of the box and went off somewhere
Even though it's slow
it can still crawl around anywhere
Then what should we do?
The sound of the Snake-Headed Monster!
It seems to have headed up the back hill
Let's go check it out
What are you doing here?
I'm so sorry!
More importantly
here are crawl tracks from the Snake-Headed Monster
We have to track it without letting it notice us
Be careful
We might bump into it along the way
What's wrong?
The Snake-Headed Monster's tracks vanished!
Watch out, it's right nearby!
Awesome, I caught the Snake-Headed Monster!
-Hooray, hooray!
You two!
What are you doing?
-Ouch!
What are you guys doing here?
Doing our sketch homework, obviously
That's right
I forgot to do my homework!
What? Something that scary escaped?
If we don't catch it soon, it's going to be a disaster!
You guys help out too
That's not my problem
This is your responsibility, Nobita
Go catch it all by yourself
Hmph, ridiculous
But we don't even know where it's hiding
Hmph, you think that's going to scare me?
Anyway...
The birds have all turned rock-hard!
Calm down, Suneo
Let's work together to catch the Snake-Headed Monster
However, approaching it recklessly is very dangerous
It might turn us into stone
Can it really do that?
Then what should we do?
Let's come up with a plan together first
First, we lure the Snake-Headed Monster out
Then we drop this box from above to catch it
Alright, leave trapping it to me
That's Gian for you!
You guys be the bait
That sounds kind of terrifying
Alright
I'll be the bait and lure the Snake-Headed Monster out
But if the Snake-Headed Monster's beam hits you...
No problem, as long as we use this
"Ordinary Mirror"
Now isn't the time to joke around
Can you be serious for once?
I am being serious
We can use this mirror to reflect the Snake-Headed Monster's beam
Oh, right
Then when the Snake-Headed Monster gets hit by its own
beam, it'll turn to stone
I see!
Everyone wait here
until I lure it out
Okay
Well, here I go
Be careful!
I don't know why, but I'm kind of worried
The Snake-Headed Monster turned it like this
It must be nearby
Snake-Headed Monster, where are you?
Come out!
Th-That sound is...
It's the Snake-Headed Monster's voice!
Don't tell me Doraemon...
Let's go
Wait!
Wait for me!
Doraemon!
Doraemon failed!
The mirror broke!
This way
we won't be able to reflect the Snake-Headed Monster's beam
If Doraemon has turned into stone
we can't ask him to take out any gadgets
This is bad!
Hey, Suneo!
What's the point of running away like this?
I'm going home!
Running home isn't going to help!
You're so annoying!
Suneo!
I can't turn to stone here!
Damn it!
Suneo turned to stone too!
What do we do? There's only two of us left
We have no choice
It's up to us now
That's right, Gian!
The Snake-Headed Monster's box!
Oh no, I left it back there!
We have to hurry back and get it!
Yeah!
Alright, as long as we have this box...
Whoa!
Nobita!
Wait for me!
No way...
Nobita!
Gian!
You turned to stone too?
What should I do?
Now I'm the only one left
Nobita!
Shizuka, why are you here?
I came here to do my sketching homework
You can't stay here any longer!
What happened?
We have to get out of here right away!
If we just go through here...
No, Shizuka!
Shizuka!
Come out, Snake-Headed Monster!
Turn everyone back right now!
My... my legs gave out...
H-Help me!
Help me!
Ouch!
That's it, I'll use this box
Put this box right over it from above
I'm falling...
Huh?
Whoa, just like that?
It's over
Nobita!
What happened?
Thank goodness!
Huh? When did it become evening?
What did I just...
Did Nobita solve this all by himself?
How on earth did he catch it?
It's truly a mystery
You kids!
Have you finished the homework I gave you?
I've already finished it!
I'm done too!
What about you, Nobita?
I haven't finished yet
Doraemon!
If you get made to stand in the hallway tomorrow
just use the Snake-Headed Monster again
How could you say that?